The past never stays dead
Rage is a action, crime, thriller film directed by Paco Cabezas.
When the Russian mob kidnaps the daughter of a reformed criminal, he
rounds up his old crew and seeks his own brand of justice.
Paul Maguire, played by Nicolas Cage.
Caitlin Maguire, played by Aubrey Shea.
Vanessa Maguire, played by Rachel Nichols.
Francis O'Connell, played by Peter Stormare.
Detective St. John, played by Danny Glover.
Kane, played by Max Ryan.
Rage, titled Tokarev in most of Europe and Australia, is a 2014 American action crime
thriller film directed by Paco Cabezas and written by Jim Agnew and Sean Keller.
The film stars Nicolas Cage, Rachel Nichols, Peter Stormare,
Danny Glover, Max Ryan, Judd Lormand and Pasha D.
Lychnikoff.
The film explores themes of bratva (russian mafia),
kidnapping, revenge, haunted by the past.
The tone is intense.